Guide to the Cherríe Moraga Papers, 1970-1996
Department of Special Collections
- Series II. Manuscripts
  - This Bridge Called My Back. "El Mundo Zurdo" [duplicate of paste-up of Luisah Teish] n. d. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - This Bridge Called My Back. "El Mundo Zurdo" [original paste-up of bios] n. d. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - This Bridge Called My Back. "El Mundo Zurdo" [duplicate of paste-up of bios] n. d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - This Bridge Called My Back:"La Guera" Master Copy n. d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    1 TMS: 12 pp.
  - This Bridge Called My Back: Assembled Draft [ 1 of 2] n. d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: Assembled Draft [ 2 of 2] n. d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: Editorial Changes and Miscellaneous Copies 1980 -1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: Script for presentation, drafts,and notes[ 1 of 4 ] n. d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: Script for presentation, drafts,and notes[ 2 of 4 ] n. d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: Script for presentation, drafts,and notes[ 3 of 4 ] n. d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: Script for presentation, drafts,and notes[ 4 of 4 ] n. d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: Script for presentation, programs n. d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors 1979 -1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Alarcón, Norma] 1980 Jan. -May (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Bambara, Toni Cade] 1981 Feb. -Mar. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Canaan, Andrea R.] 1979 Oct. -1980 May (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Carillo, Jo] 1980 May (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Clarke, Cheryl] 1979 Oct. -1980 June (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Daniels, Gabrielle] 1980 Mar. -May (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Davenport, Doris] 1980 Mar. -Sept. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Littlebear, Naomi] 1980 Jan. -Mar. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Lorde, Audre] 1979 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Morales, Rosario] 1979 Sept. -1980 June (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Moschkovich, Judit] 1981 Jan. -Feb. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Noda, Barbara] 1980 Feb. -June (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Persephone Press] 1981 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Smith, Barbara] 1979 Oct. -1980 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Smith, Beverly] 1979 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Wong, Nellie] 1981 May (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence with contributors [Yamada, Mitsuye] 1979 Oct. -1980 June (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: correspondence and responses 1981 -1982 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: unidentified correspondence 1979 -1980 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - This Bridge Called My Back: Book jacket and other graphics n. d. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "By word of mouth," The Great Midwestern Book Show, 1984, pp. 6; 16 1984 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - "Cervezita; or, quit while you're a head": research materials [1 of 2] n. d. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "Cervezita; or, quit while you're a head": research materials [2 of 2] n. d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Chicanas Speak out for Tomorrow" n. d. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    1 TMs
  - "The Chicano Codices": research for article [ 1 of 3] n. d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - "The Chicano Codices": research for article, photographs, and color photocopies [ 2 of 3] n. d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "The Chicano Codices": research for article [ 3 of 3] n. d. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "The Chicano Codices": poems, notes n. d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): first draft 1995 May 15 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): draft for the East Palo Alto reading 1995 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Circle in the Dirt"(EPAP): draft 1995 Oct. 5 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Circle in the Dirt"(EPAP): draft 1995 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): draft for production 1995 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Marva Als n. d. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Jennifer Espinoza. 1993 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Daniela Gomez. 1994 Oct. 21 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Daniela Gomez and Chavela Rivera. 1994 Oct. 21 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with "EPA parents at English Night Class" 1994 Nov. 2 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interviews with Joanna Caballero, Andrea Chacon, Mariela Chacon. 1994 Nov. 7 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interviews with Avelar, B.; Clark, B.; Garcia, B. and D.; Gibson, R. 1995 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Circle in the Dirt" (EPAP): Interviews with Dumont, E.; Hall, H.; Johnson, T.; Peraza, G.; Uhila, D. 1995 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interviews with Eads, M. T.; Knox, H.; Princess of Tonga; Wilmore, J. 1995 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Ruben Abrica / Latino Community Council n. d. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Estele Avelar n. d. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Ruben Avelar n. d. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Edward Jomo and Sandili Becks n. d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Yen Bui Tran n. d. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - "Circle in the Dirt" (EPAP): Interview with Nevida Butler n. d. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Trevor Burrowes n. d. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with James Calloway at Sanford's Restaurant n. d. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Barbara Clark n. d. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interviews with Emily and Carroll Damant n. d. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Bob Garcia n. d. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Anthony Moore. n. d. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Barbara Mouton. n. d. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Leroy Musgraves. n. d. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Albert Nakai. n. d. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interviews with people on the street. n. d. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interviews with Susie Rodriguez, Jacqueline Lazu, Linda S. Ramos n. d. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Gertrude Wilks n. d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Interview with Tesuuko Yakanishi n. d. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): research materials on East Palo Alto history and landscape n. d. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): research materials; profile of familia/pina by Ibarra and Valdiosera n. d. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): research materials on Ohlone Indian history n. d. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): research materials, Ohlone Indian presentation n. d. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): research materials: "Oyamo's script, second draft" n. d. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): transcript of EPA Latino Community Council Meeting 1993 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "Circle in the Dirt" (EPAP): transcript of "Muwekma means 'the people'" 1994 Dec. 4 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPA/LARA): Transcription notes of interviews and production notes 1995 Jan. 23 -1995 Mar. 7 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): transcript of production 1995 Nov. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): transcript notes 1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Script, "Muwekma means 'the people'" 1994 May 21 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): Notes and Miscellaneous, 1994 May 21 - 1995 Nov. 20 n. d. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Circle in the Dirt: PIP (Play-in-Progress) 1994 Nov. 19 -1995 May 3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): extra credit plays by Stanford students 1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): miscellaneous business 1994 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP): treatments, summaries, correspondence, and articles 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Circle in the Dirt: "Scatter the Wind," [La Obra] 1995 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Circle in the Dirt: "'She's got huevos, man': East Palo Alto." [Scripts - 1/LA OBRA 1] 1995 May 10 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Circle in the Dirt: "Understudies to the universe: The People of East Palo Alto". [La Obra 5/12] 1995 May 11 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Circle in the Dirt: "La Obra: The People of East Palo Alto." [La Obra 5/13] 1995 May 12 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "Circle in the Dirt": "A Pueblo Tale" [La Obra 5/15] 1995 May 14 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Circle in the Dirt (EPAP) 1995 May 15 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Circle in the Dirt: "El Pueblo de East Palo Alto." [Scripts- 1 LA/OBRA 2] 1995 July 11 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Circle in the Dirt: production notes 1995 Sept. 29 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Circle in the Dirt: "El Pueblo de East Palo Alto." [C.I.D. In-prog. Fall 95] 1995 Oct. 25 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Circle in the Dirt: premiere version 1995 Nov. 10-Dec. 18 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Coatlicue's Call: early drafts 1990 Feb. -Apr. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Coatlicue's Call: early drafts 1990 Summer (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Coatlicue's Call: "master" copy 1990 Oct. 12 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Coatlicue's Call: notas and early drafts 1989 Nov. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Coatlicue's Call: tech copy 1990 Oct. 12 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Coatlicue's Call: research and source material n. d. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - "Codex Xeri: El Momento historico," The Chicano Codices: Encountering art of the Americas. San Francisco: Mexican Museum n.d. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    reprint
  - Commencement Address, Oakes College; University of California, Santa Cruz [adaptation] n. d. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Cuca Contreras, Beast of Burden: comic scenario, INTAR workshop n. d. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Cuentos: escritos por Latinas / translated by María Isabel Rivera S. 1989 Oct. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    TMs, 94 pp. ANS
  - Cuentos: Stories by Latinas: miscellaneous notes n. d. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Dance of the Nebula n.d. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    octavo edition reprint
  - Entre nosotras: a personal response to the 13th Inernational Lesbian and Gay Conference in Acapulco. 1991 June 30 -July 7 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Epilogue to a Christmas Story n. d. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - La Extranjera (Susana): INTAR workshop, early version 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - La Extranjera (The Foreigner): A Music Play n. d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - From a long line of Vendidas: Chicanas and Feminism n. d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    2 TMs: 27 pp.
  - La Fuerza Femenina: Artistas en Aztlan [Coyolxauhqui] 1991 July 19 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Giving up the ghost: typescript for Mission Cultural Center 1986 -1987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Giving up the ghost: Pre-Rhinoceros Version 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Giving up the ghost: working version for Rhinoceros 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Giving up the ghost: materials for publication 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Giving up the Ghost 1991 Fall (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Giving up the Ghost 1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popul Vuh Story: Correspondence with and information about Ralph Lee 1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: correspondence and Glen Velez bio 1992 -1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: Scenario / scenework-in-progress. [Version 1- Jan. 1993] 1993 Jan. -Mar. 29 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story. Scenario/ scenework-in-progress. [Version 2- April 93] 1993 Mar. 30 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: notes 1993 Apr. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: All My relations: The Story of the Dawning of the Mayor. [Version 3- May 93] 1993 May 8 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: [Version 4- June 93] 1994 Jan. 5 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: Fifth Rewrite: January 94 [Version 5 - Jan. 94] 1994 Jan. 24 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: Version 6: January 25, 1994 1994 Jan. 27 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: draft c. 1994 Jan. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: draft 1994 Jan. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: Fifth rewrite 1994 Jan. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: typescripts and notes 1994 Feb. -July (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: Quiche notes / adds 1994 July 6 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: a typescript for Julliard performances 1994 July (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: Version 7: Julliard Performances, July 14-15, 1994 1994 July 7 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Heart of the Earth: a Popol Vuh story: NEA Application 1994 Aug. 30 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: a typescript for Jim Henson Puppet Festival 1994 Sept. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Heart of the Earth: a Popol Vuh story: synopsis 1994 Oct. 6 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: typescript for INTAR and promotional materials production 1994 Oct. -1995 Jan. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Heart of the Earth: A Popol Vuh story: INTAR production. 1996 Mar. 21 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Heroes and Saints: pre-first draft scenes and notes 1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Heroes and Saints: original version 1989 Oct. 16 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Heroes and Saints: version 2 1989 Nov. 26 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Heroes and Saints: second version sent to LATC 1989 Dec. 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Heroes and Saints: draft [1 of 2] 1991 Apr. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Heroes and Saints: draft [2 of 2] 1991 Apr. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Heroes and Saints: version for LATA's staged readings series 1991 Apr. 28 -30 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Heroes and Saints: draft 1991 May (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Heroes and Saints: rehearsal / production version 1992 Mar. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Heroes and Saints: Brava! Production copy 1992 May (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Heroes and Saints: post-opening version done at San Antonio 1992 Spring (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Heroes and Saints 1992 Summer (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Heroes and Saints: version for submission / publication 1993 Jan. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Heroes and Saints and other plays ["Giving up the ghost" and "Shadow of a man"], manuscript for publication [1 of 2] 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Heroes and Saints and other plays ["Giving up the ghost" and "Shadow of a man"], manuscript for publication [2 of 2] 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - INTAR workshop: picture of binder cover 1984 -1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - INTAR workshop: notas 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - INTAR workshop: Lourdes and Yolanda [dialogue excerpts] 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - INTAR workshop: Ricardo and Lourdes [dialogue excerpts] 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - INTAR workshop: "Two Women" [dialogue excerpts] 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - INTAR workshop: miscellaneous copies and drafts 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Last Generation: Research Materials [Utne Reader.--No. 52: "On the importance of being tribal"] 1992 Jul. -Aug. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - The Last Generation: materials for publication 1992 Feb. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Last Generation: notes and drafts n. d. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - The Last Generation: drafts for "Breakdown of Bicultural Mind" n. d. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - The Last Generation: draft of "Our Lady of the Cannery Workers" n. d. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - The Last Generation: corrected drafts of "Queer Aztlán: The Reformation of the Chicano Tribe." n. d. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - The Last Generation: draft of "The Saving of America; a Chicana Lesbian Response to the Quincentennial" 1991 Nov. 22 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - The Last Generation: draft of "Tales of Manhattan" n. d. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - The Last Generation: drafts of "Meditating on 'La Llorona'" n. d. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - The Last Generation: drafts [1 of 5] n. d. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - The Last Generation: drafts [2 of 5] n. d. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - The Last Generation: drafts [3 of 5] n. d. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - The Last Generation: drafts [4 of 5] n. d. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - The Last Generation: drafts [5 of 5] n. d. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - The Last Generation: corrected bound draft n. d. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - The Last Generation: galley proofs n. d. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - The Lesbian Scene: script and dialogue 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Living and Loving in the Shadows n. d. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "La Malinche" [An except from "A Long Line of Vendidas"], New York Native (1983 Oct. 10-23), pp. 36-37. 1983 Oct 10-23 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - McDonald's in Moscow 1991 Apr. 22 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Mother Poems 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - "Mother's Day," 1981. Boston. Coming Up. -- 1981 Nov. 1981 Nov. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - NCASA Introduction n. d. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Neither slaves nor Masters: Reflections for the Nineties 1989 May 25 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Notes toward an Introduction to Racism Forum, 1980 Sept. 1980 Sept. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - The Obedient Daughter: Estela Portillo Trambley's Trini 1986 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - On the Subject of Lesbianism & Sexism 1978 Oct. 14 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Poem of the Rock n. d. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: copy of the 2nd edition of This Bridge Called My Back, with notes for translation n. d. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: introduction and front matter and pre-translation notes n. d. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: chapter 1 (pre-translation) n. d. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: chapter II (pre-translation) n. d. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: chapter III (pre-translation) n. d. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: assembled drafts [1 of 7] n. d. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: assembled drafts [2 of 7] n. d. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: assembled drafts [3 of 7] n. d. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: assembled drafts [4 of 7] n. d. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: assembled drafts [5 of 7] n. d. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: assembled drafts [6of 7] n. d. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: assembled drafts & misc. items [7 of 7] n. d. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: galleys n. d. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: contributor information [bio sketches, correspondence] [ 1 of 2] n. d. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: contributor information [bio sketches, correspondence] [ 2 of 2] n. d. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: contributor information, permission forms n. d. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: correspondence with Daniel Fogel, ISM Press 1986 Aug. -1988 July (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: graphics, art 1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: introduction n. d. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Esta Puente mi Espalda: "new articles to consider" n. d. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Esta puente mi espalda: translations in progress 1976 Oct. 27 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    TMs, 6 pp.
  - Except from "Queer Aztlan: The Re-formation of Chicano Tribe," In out of the Cold. 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Recurring themes in Chic(a) Lit. n.d. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Shadow of A Man: early versions of "Cooky/Lupita" n. d. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Shadow of A Man: Early Versions of Hortensia/Amalia n. d. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Shadow of A Man: early versions of Leticia/Marisa n. d. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Shadow of A Man: early versions of Rodrigo/Manuelcito n. d. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Shadow of A Man: early versions of misc. extracts [1 of 2] n. d. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Shadow of A Man: early versions of misc. extracts [2 of 2] n. d. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Shadow of A Man: misc. scenes and notes [1 of 2] 1985 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Shadow of a Man: Misc. scenes and notes [2 of 2] 1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Shadow of A Man: working draft 1988 winter (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Shadow of A Man: LATC in-progress draft 1989 Feb. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Shadow of A Man: LATC disc version 1989 Feb. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Shadow of A Man at ACT: business misc. 1989 Mar. -Apr. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Shadow of A Man: pre-ACT version 1989 Apr. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Shadow of A Man: reject scenes, ACT 1989 Apr. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Shadow of A Man: post ACT 1989 May 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Shadow of A Man: version sent to Fornes Women's Theatre 1989 Aug. 26 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Shadow of A Man: bound draft 1989 Aug. 26 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Shadow of A Man: facsimile 1990 Mar. 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Shadow of A Man: journal and play notes 1990 June (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Shadow of A Man: misc. excerpts and notes [1 of 2] 1990 Aug. 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Shadow of A Man: Misc. excerpts and notes [2 of 2] 1990 Aug. 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Shadow of A Man 1990 Sept. 10 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Shadow of A Man: Eureka Theatre Company, miscellaneous notes and assembled drafts. c. 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Shadow of A Man: Eureka's copy c. 1991 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Shadow of A Man: post-Eureka script 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Shadow of A Man: South Coast Repertory Theatre Version ["post- ACT"] n. d. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - "A Tough Cookie," Sojourner (1985 July), p. 30. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - "Unified Rainbow of Strength": conference speech n. d. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - La Vision: The history of love and the loveless 1987 Fall (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Wanting it: It was in my genes to love like this, article for The Advocate. 1985 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Watsonville: research, "A Crisis of Democracy", diss. by Paule Cruz Takash, pp. 1-74 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Watsonville: research on "A Crisis of Democracy", diss. by Paule Cruz Takash, pp. 75-146 1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Watsonville: research on "A Crisis of Democracy", diss. by Paule Cruz Takash, pp. 142-216 1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Watsonville: research on "A Crisis of Democracy", diss. by Paule Cruz Takash, pp. 217- 294 1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Watsonville: research on Paule Cruz Takash, "A Crisis of Democracy," pp. 295-414 1990 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Watsonville: notas and research, misc. n. d. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Watsonville: notas and research and misc., Fornes Workshop n. d. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Watsonville: drafts 1994 Nov. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Watsonville: drafts 1994 Nov. 21 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Watsonville: drafts, Jewish Travelling Theater 1995 June 8 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Watsonville: drafts 1995 July (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Watsonville: drafts, South Coast Repertory 1995 July -Aug. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Watsonville: drafts, South Coast Repertory 1995 Aug. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Watsonville: drafts with notations 1994 Nov. 24 (Box 18, Folder 7)